[{"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "What is happening right now?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "Just four days ago we were talking about wind chills.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "What is going on with the East Coast weather?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Well, of course we've got these major extremes and the transition during spring typically produces this type of extreme weather.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Is this as extraordinary as it seems to me, Amy, or not?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "We're heading to a particularly extreme hurricane season, according to the Hurricane Center, 13 to 20 named storms, almost double possibly the number of hurricanes, and double possibly the number of major hurricanes.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Chad, are we heading towards a particularly extreme summer, do you think?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Well, there are two separate cases, actually, both involving ricin letters.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Are the FBI in the belief that it's all the same person?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Well, it's intended I think to attract publicity which it certainly is, intended to potentially intimidate but quite clearly the president and the mayor are not going to be intimidated by it.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "What do you make of this latest ricin letter attack on the president and on Mayor Bloomberg?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Well, that is the concern.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "How worried would you be if you were running the FBI or an organization like that now or even a city police force, how worrying is it that it's so easy now to make guns, bombs, poison?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "Really nothing.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "What can you do about such blatant, emblazon incitement to violence in a publication?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "It's having a very comprehensive investigation conducted by both the FBI and the Massachusetts State Police that there's an old adage in policing, the first story is never the correct story.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "Would you think this needs a police investigation?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "Hey, Piers.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Donnie, how are you?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I was on set on my TV series \"Blue Bloods\" in New York and was surrounded by New Yorkers.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "Where were you when you heard about the Boston marathon bombings and what was your first reaction?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Well, it's frightening.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "And Donnie, when you discovered that the perpetrators of this atrocity were two young brothers who had been living in Boston for quite a long time and had suddenly committed this outrage, what was your view of that?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "It's a wonderful feeling, Piers.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "How do you feel about being able to put on such an amazing show in your own city for your own people?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "Well, there's nothing -- there's no real way to adequately respond or to minister or -- you know, I don't even think we can really understand entirely what's happened.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "What do you say to them to try and make their lives a little better?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "I hope the people in charge of the concert who have been in direct contact with the families will have a sense of what -- how they need it the most and what's the most effective way to distribute it.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "What do you think from all you've gleaned about the way the money should be spent is going to be the most effective way of using this large amount of cash?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Well, I was born here.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "And James, finally for you, what does it mean to you to be a Bostonian?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Well, my understanding is that Brian Panitch, the lawyer for Katherine Jackson and Michael's children, who incidentally I recommended to Katherine as the best lawyer in the country to handle this case, he's been going over e-mails with Mr. Gongaware and I'm told that Mr. Gongaware is professing not to remember exactly why he did the mail or what he meant, answering very often I don't recall, I don't recall, I don't recall.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "What was going on?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Well, it's a problem, Piers, because when a witness continues to say, says over and over, I don't recall, as apparently this witness has, then it starts to give the impression of untruthfulness to the jury and, in fact, it's reported that the jury began to laugh when this witness continued to say, I don't recall, and when the jury begins to laugh at the witness, it should be a cause for concern by the defense that perhaps the jury's thinking this witness is just not credible.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Is it any defense to say you don't recall sending an e-mail when there's a copy of the e-mail sitting in court?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's a tragedy for this family and I think the heat is going to be so intense on the Mexican government that she'll be released at some point.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Tom, what do you make of this case?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "Well, I would do just exactly what was done today and CNN in fact have seen what I'm going to call the smoking video.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "If this was your client, though, what would you be doing now to try and put the maximum type of pressure on to the Mexican authorities to get her out of there?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "I dismiss the premise, the idea that these were scandals.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Did you ever think you'd have to deal with three scandals like this at the same time?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "The obvious question, Margaret Hoover, are they scandals?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "How scandalized can they be if that's what they want him to do?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Because the American people know that even if there are scandals, they're not presidential scandals, they have nothing to do with him.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Why is he getting more popular through this period rather than less?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I think you need an independent -- I think you need an independent people --", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Should Eric Holder resign?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "It is a --", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "A God-given right?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "Well, and -- yes, it is a constitutional right.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "How about a constitutional right?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "You know, here's the deal, Piers.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Is it a God-given right?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "This -- no, it is not a God-given right.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Yes or no?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "You've always --", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Is it surprising that you're getting some people now flipping and doing this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "ILL: Well, there are a lot of people who believe that these are natural rights and these inalienable constitutional rights are given to us because we are endowed them by our Creator.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "I was curious about his link -- you know, some -- not just constitutional right but a God-given right?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "Is he a nut, though, being driven, whoever this person is, by nutty rhetoric from extremists?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "I think it could, but the difference between that and say civil rights or that and these other issues is big money.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Do you think it's one of those things that in the end it will change?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "That's actually what it is.", "docId": "130530pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "Good thing we have to be with you, right?", "qSentId": 592}]